it's Tuesday October 21st 2014 and here
這是2014年10月21日星期二和這裡
are the stories were covering this week
這個故事本週都有報導
the BBC will be exposing articles
BBC將揭露文章
removed from google by the right to be
谷歌被權利移除
forgotten rule Smart Meters can be
被遺忘的規則Smart Meters 可以
hacked to reduce your utility bill
黑客入侵以減少您的水電費
offline access to Internet content is
離線訪問Internet內容是
coming to areas of the world with no
來到世界各地沒有
internet access and a proof-of-concept
互聯網接入和概念驗證
worm has demonstrated that an attacker
蠕蟲已經證明了攻擊者
could take control of home data storage
可以控製家庭數據存儲
these stories are coming right up don't
這些故事馬上就來不
go anywhere operation christmas child is
去任何地方操作聖誕節孩子
one of the great stories it's unfolding
它正在展開的偉大故事之一
in our lifetime
在我們的一生中
we are only seeing just the beginning of
我們只是看到了它的開始
this project and these children will
這個項目和這些孩子會
change the world
改變世界
the BBC is to publish a continually
BBC將不斷發布
updated list of its articles removed
更新了其文章的更新列表
from Google under the controversial
來自谷歌的爭議
right to be forgotten rule the ruling
被遺忘的權利統治了這一裁決
allows people to ask Google to remove
允許人們要求Google刪除
some types of information about them
關於它們的某些類型的信息
from its search index but editorial
來自其搜索索引，但編輯
policy had David Jordan told a public
政策讓大衛喬丹告訴公眾
meeting hosted by google that the BBC
由谷歌主持的BBC會議
felt some of its articles had been
覺得它的一些文章已經存在
wrongly hidden mr. Jordan claims that
錯誤地隱藏了先生。約旦聲稱
the BBC had so far been notified of 46
到目前為止，英國廣播公司已被通知46
links to articles that had been removed
鏈接到已刪除的文章
in the next few weeks the BBC will begin
在接下來的 幾週內 ，BBC將開始
publishing the list of removed URLs it
發布已移除的URL列表
has been notified about by Google mr.
已被谷歌先生 通知 過 。
Jordan said greater care should be given
約旦表示應該給予更多的關注
to the public's right to remember many
公眾有權記住許多人
utility companies are installing remote
公用事業公司正在安裝遠程
meters to help customers monitor and
米來幫助客戶監控和
manage their power use and help them be
管理他們的用電並幫助他們
more energy-efficient have your videl is
你的 videl更節能
an independent researcher who along with
獨立的研究人員
Alberto elara has found flaws in the
Alberto elara發現了瑕疵
smart meters he says we took them apart
智能電錶他說我們將它們拆開了
to see how they work what he found has
看看他們發現了什麼
raised some concerns at the utility
對公用事業提出了一些擔憂
companies smart meters can be hacked to
公司智能電錶可以入侵
underreport energy use this essentially
少報的能源使用這實質上
means with a little know-how and very
意味著一點點訣竅和非常
little scruples you could effectively
你可以有效地顧忌
cut your electricity bill attackers
削減你的電費攻擊者
could use what the pair found to
可以使用這對發現的東西
underreport energy use or to get someone
少報的能源使用或找人
else to pay their bills by using their
否則用他們的賬單支付賬單
ID and messages sent back to the nodes
ID和消息發送回節點
that log usage with more with more work
隨著更多的工作，更多的日誌使用
researchers claim they might be paused
研究人員稱他們可能會被暫停
it might be possible to find a way to
有可能找到一種方法
seek out meters and cut off the power
尋找米並切斷電源
that they are supplying essentially the
他們提供的基本上是
warning is that poorly protected the
警告是，保護得不好
warning is that poorly protected
警告是保護不力
credentials inside the devices could let
設備內部的憑據可以讓
attackers can take control of the
攻擊者可以 控制
gadgets the utility company that
那個公用事業公司的小工具
deployed the meters are now improving
部署的儀表現在正在改善
the device's security to help protect
設備的安全性有助於保護
its network
它的網絡
can an entire library be put in your
可以把整個圖書館放進你的
pocket most people would say yes all you
口袋里大多數人都會說你是的
need is a mobile phone with access to
需要的是一部 可以訪問的手機
the Internet but what about for the many
互聯網 ，但怎麼樣了許多
people in the world that lack Internet
世界上缺乏互聯網的人
connectivity the answer can still be yes
連接答案仍然是肯定的
according to Syed Kareem who explained
據Syed Kareem解釋說
the nature of his company Outernet at
他的公司Outernet的性質
Ted global the business aims to address
泰德全球業務旨在解決
the fact that about two-thirds of the
這一事實的約三分之二
world's population has no internet
世界人口沒有互聯網
access he told the BBC when you talk
當你說話時他告訴BBC
about the internet you talk about two
關於互聯網你談到兩個
main functions communication and
主要功能溝通和
information access it's the
信息訪問它是
communication part that makes it so
這樣做的溝通部分
expensive so Outernet focuses instead on
昂貴所以Outernet專注於
information the project aims to create a
該項目旨在創建一個信息
core archive of the world's most
世界上最核心的檔案館
valuable knowledge called from websites
從網站上傳來的寶貴知識
including wikipedia and Project
包括維基百科和項目
Gutenberg a collection of copyright free
古騰堡 收藏的版權免費
ebooks this would be updated on roughly
電子書將大致更新
a monthly basis it would also provide
每個月它 也會提供
more time sensitive content including
更多時間敏感的內容包括
news bulletins and disaster alerts that
新聞公告和災難警報
could be updated several times an hour
可以每小時更新幾次
all this information would then be
所有這些信息都將是
broadcast via satellites and picked up
通過衛星廣播並接收
by equipment on the ground which in turn
依靠地上的設備
creates Wi-Fi hotspots allowing the data
創建允許數據的Wi-Fi熱點
to be accessed by individual smartphones
個人智能手機訪問
and computers a small village in central
和計算機中央的一個小村莊
Africa for example mr. Kareem said one
非洲，例如先生。 卡里姆說了一句
hotspot could provide dozens of books
熱點可以提供數十本書
and other information two to three
和其他信息二到三
hundred people living close by mr.
住在附近的百人
Kareem said the system was currently
卡里姆說目前這個系統
capable of broadcasting 200 megabytes of
能夠播放200兆字節的
data per day but his intention is to
每天的數據，但他的意圖是
increase that to 100 gigabytes or more
增加到100千兆字節或更多
he said we want to use as much existing
他說我們想要使用盡可能多的存在
technology and repurpose it a bit so
技術並重新調整它的用途
that people buy as little stuff as
人們買的東西就像
possible Mark Newman from the technology
可能是Mark Newman的技術
research firm ovum believes the idea to
研究公司卵子相信這個想法
be an interesting one but expresses
是一個有趣的，但表達
concern over literacy issues he says
他說，對掃盲問題的關注
delivery by audio rather than text would
通過音頻而不是文本傳送
be something to look at but that would
要看的 東西 ，但那會
use up more data while companies like
公司喜歡用盡更多數據
Facebook hope to bring the Internet to
Facebook希望將互聯網帶到
these areas mr. Korean believes that
這些 地區先生。韓國人認為
broadcasting data offline could be a
離線廣播數據可能是一個
better way to bypass censorship and
繞過審查制度的更好方法
distribute knowledge we
我們分發知識
checked and his conviction is legit
檢查，他的信念是合法的
Outernet even allows you to download the
外網甚至允許你下載
entire archive directly from their
整個檔案直接來自他們的
website Outernet dot is a malicious worm
網站Outernet dot是一種惡意蠕蟲
that can roam the net seeking data
可以在網上尋找數據
stored on insecure Hardware has been
存儲在不安全的硬件上已經 存在
created by security researcher the
由安全研究員創建的
proof-of-concept worm was written to
編寫了 概念驗證 蠕蟲
illustrate how vulnerable these data
說明了這些數據的脆弱性
stores are to malicious attack the worm
商店是惡意攻擊蠕蟲
can exploit the many bugs research
可以利用許多錯誤研究
researcher Jacob Holcomb found in
研究員Jacob Holcomb找到了
popular home data systems already he
他已經流行的家庭數據系統
said there was evidence cyber criminals
據說網絡罪犯有證據
had noticed how easy it was to exploit
已經註意到利用它是多麼容易
these data stores mr. Holcomb started
這些數據存儲先生。 霍爾科姆開始了
the work on the started to work on the
在開始工作， 在工作
worm after carrying out a series of
蠕蟲進行了一系列的
tests on network attached storage nas
網絡附加存儲測試
systems made by 10 separate
系統由10個獨立製成
manufacturers many people connect to
製造商很多人都聯繫到
these devices to give a home router to a
這些設備給家用路由器一個
home router to give family members a
家庭路由器給家庭成員一個
place to put important files such as
地方把重要的文件， 如
photos and films or to act as a back up
照片和電影或作為備份
against other gadgets some home routers
針對其他小工具的一些家用路由器
can also connect to hard drives to turn
也可以連接硬盤轉
them into NASA type devices mr.
他們進入NASA型設備先生。
Holcomb's investigation revealed 30
霍爾科姆的調查顯示30
separate undocumented vulnerabilities in
單獨的未記錄的漏洞
the NAS devices many of these if
NAS設備很多這些如果
exploited would give an attacker
被利用會給攻擊者
complete control over a device letting
完全控制設備租用
them plunder the data on it or use it in
他們掠奪數據或使用它
a way to get at other devices in that
一種獲取其他設備的方法
home network and spy on what people did
家庭網絡和間諜人們做了什麼
online most of the exploitable products
在線大多數可利用的產品
he found where in the web-based
他找到了基於網絡的地方
interface interface typically used to
接口接口通常用於
administer these devices all your tech
管理這些設備所有技術
news with a slight Linux bias visit the
有輕微 Linux偏見的 消息 訪問了
category 5 TV news room at newsroom
新聞室的5類電視新聞室
category 5 TV for the category 5 TV
5類電視的5類電視
i stashed it through made us
我把它藏起來了